Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 8=
Madam, the City Lord
stayed outside all night.
He's still there.
If he insists on staying,
let him be.
Let me see. Isn't it beautiful?
Qiming, what are you doing?
Forgive me.
Mother,
please stop forcing Miss Yu to marry me.
Miss Yu didn't ask me to say this.
It has nothing to do with her.
This is my own decision.
I've always given you
everything you wanted.
Have I ever failed you?
You won't marry the girl you love.
What do you want?
Mother, ever since
my sister went missing,
you've been seeking
her reflection through me.
You've always offered me the best,
and you do love me.
But your love weighs on me.
I can't bear it.
You've piled the love
for my sister onto me as well.
You want me to be filial, considerate,
obedient, and sensible.
But have you ever
considered what I truly desire?
You've never had an opinion.
When did you ever want something?
Mother, I'm grateful you raised me.
But I don't want
to rush into marriage so blindly.
Miss Yu doesn't love me.
So, I can't marry her.
If one day
she says she loves me
and wants to marry me,
that will be the time
for us to get married.
You...
Qiming, you've matured.
I will do as you say.
Since Qiming won't pressure you,
forget about the wedding.
In the end, I'm not meant to be
your mother-in-law.
Madam.
May I ask you
for something?
What are you doing?
I met Mr. Song too late
and I need more time to know him.
But if you don't disdain me,
will you be my godmother first?
If you don't answer,
I'll take it as a yes.
You...
Fine.
Cone on. Get up.
Is that a yes?
From now on, I'll call you Godmother.
Godmother, please sit.
Let me massage your shoulders.
Don't be like this.
We're like family.
Godmother, how's the pressure?
Wan.
Since you've divorced the City Lord,
stay here at Shili Pavilion
if you don't wish to go back
to your home.
Alright, Godmother.
Godmother.
Actually, there's
one more thing I must do.
Thank you.
(Recruitment)
Welcome
to the unprecedented,
utterly unique,
and unmatched
Yu's Courier
for delivery and errand services.
Liu Bingmo.
Coming.
(Yu's Courier)
It's our first day in business.
Let's work together from now on,
grow stronger, and achieve new glory.
We have a bright future.
Are you confident?
- Yes!
My lord.
What's wrong?
Madam didn't marry Mr. Song.
What did you say?
She didn't marry him.
She's at West Street.
Will you go see her?
She didn't marry him.
Wan.
Move aside.
Make way.
Look who we have here.
The City Lord's wife
started a business, huh?
I've already divorced
the City Lord.
Remember my name.
I'm the owner of Yu's Courier,
Yu Yingwan.
You divorced the City Lord
and came to
compete with common folk like us?
You're just a woman.
Can you even run a business?
Yeah, can you?
Want trouble?
Liu Bingmo.
Whether I can run a business
isn't for you to question.
That's enough. Get lost.
Don't mess with my business.
Yeah, get lost.
You want a fight?
Say that again.
Take it easy.
You're a woman.
Marry someone
and have children.
Stop showing up
in public, right?
You only care about
marrying someone and having children.
What are you
doing for yourself?
No wonder people say you're ill-mannered
and got dumped.
You're so sharp-tongued.
Men don't like you.
Exactly.
Many people appreciate
this sharp tongue of mine.
Besides,
I don't need men's approval to live.
I'm living life on my own terms.
And remember.
I chose to divorce the City Lord.
I dumped Mu Yunqing.
Y-You...
You brought ill fate to your in-laws.
Nobody wants you.
I'll count to three.
Get lost or I'll get the authorities.
You...
What are you doing? Open up.
Open up. It's not City Lord's Mansion.
My lady.
My lord.
We're divorced.
Why did you come to my shop?
Didn't you marry Song Qiming?
Why are you here?
I...
I changed my mind.
Why should I tell you?
Song Qiming isn't the one for you.
Let's go home.
No.
Lord Mu.
I'm not going back with you.
Things are perfect at Shili Pavilion.
Besides, we're divorced.
I can't go back with you.
We're not divorced.
Lord Mu,
I don't love you anymore.
Please leave.
Let me go.
Calmer now?
If you don't let go,
I'll call for help.
You scoundrel.
Wan, I made a mistake.
When this is over,
I'll explain everything.
Every word is sincere, I swear.
Trust me.
I can't live without you.
Then tell me.
What's your deal with Luo Shishi?
I did try to approach her.
(This is incense from Mobei.)
Miss Luo,
could you tell me
where you obtained
the incense in your room?
But I did that for a reason.
Trust me.
How can I trust you?
(Code of Male Virtues)
Code of Male Virtues.
A husband...
Keep it down. Don't read out loud.
A husband should uphold moral virtue.
Always please your wife.
Be punished if you cheat.
Alright, from now on,
I won't let you off
if you break even one
of these rules.
Come home with me tonight.
That depends on my mood.
Wan, you're back.
I'm just grabbing some clothes.
Wan, I have a gift for you.
What is it?
A lotus emerges pure from clear waters,
unadorned by artifice.
This hairpin suits you perfectly.
It's just a hairpin.
What's so special about it?
So pretty.
Are you done?
May I leave now?
Wan, come back home, please.
I promise
I won't treat you like before.
Really?
The person
who abducted me
left me at Shili Pavilion
for Madam Hong to keep me there.
I must find out who this person is.
Don't worry.
I'll look into it.
I can investigate too.
After all, I have
certain advantages you don't.
Wan.
Stop investigating
that totem, okay?
I'm going back there.
Can't you stay?
Not today. We'll talk tomorrow.
(Can I really
change everything this time?)
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪